chiwallisdress.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Notice : Buy Chi Chi Dress,River Island,Wallis Dress for Less, Chic Wallis Dress Uk Sale

This Privacy Policy sets out the manner in which Sporting Life collects, uses, discloses and otherwise manages the personal information of our customers. 

What information do we collect and how do we use it?

We may collect personal information when you:

Purchase or return products on our Website or in one of our Stores;  
Create an account on our Website;  
Request services on our Website, such as our Wish List and Gift Lists;  
Sign-up to receive promotional e-mail or other communications from us;  
Use the “E-mail a Friend” or other similar features on our Website;  
Contact us with a comment, question or complaint.

Product Purchases & Returns: When you make a purchase on the Website, we collect personal information such as your name, e-mail address, shipping and billing address as well as your payment information. We use this information to process and fulfil you order.

Customer Service: If you contact us with a comment, question or complaint, you may be asked for information that identifies you (such as your name, address and a phone number) along with additional information we need to help us promptly answer your question or respond to your comment, question or complaint. We may retain this information to assist you in the future and to improve our customer service, product and service offerings.

Do we use Cookies and other Tracking mechanisms?

In general, you can visit our Website without telling us who you are or submitting any personal information. However, we collect the IP (Internet protocol) addresses of all visitors to our Website and other related information such as page requests, browser type, operating system and average time spent on our Website. We use this information to help us understand our Website activity, and to monitor and improve our Website.

Cookies: Our Website uses a technology called "cookies". A cookie is a tiny element of data that our Website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return.For example, if you have an account, these cookies may let us know who you are and will provide us with information that we use to personalize our Website in accordance with your preferences. You may set your Web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to not accept certain cookies. However, you may find that certain parts of our Website will not function without the use of cookies.  

Advertising: Cookies, web beacons, tracer tags and similar technologies help us to improve, deliver, and understand how you use our Website and the ads that are served to you on and off the Website. For example, we may use third-party ad networks to serve our ads on other websites. These ad networks may use cookies, tracer tags or web beacons to report certain information about your visits to our Website and the websites that advertise and feature links to our Website, in order to serve and measure the effectiveness of our ads. In addition, ads appearing on our Website may be delivered to users by third-party ad networks, which may use cookies or similar technologies. These cookies allow the ad network to recognize your browser each time they serve you an ad. This information allows ad networks to tailor ads that may be of interest to you. 

To whom do we disclose information?

We will not disclose, trade, rent, sell or otherwise transfer your personal information, without your consent, except as otherwise set out herein.

Service Providers:

We may transfer (or otherwise make available) your personal information to our affiliates and other third parties who provide services on our behalf. For example, we may use service providers to authorize and process payments, host our Website, operate certain of its features, serve advertisements on our Website, send e-mail, conduct customer research, and manage and analyze data and our advertising effectiveness. Any access to your personal information by our affiliates or service providers will be limited to that necessary for them to perform their designated functions and we do not authorize them to use or disclose your personal information for their own marketing purposes. We and our service providers may also use your personal information for fraud detection and prevention purposes.

Your personal information may be maintained and processed by our affiliates and other third party service providers in the US or other jurisdictions. For additional information about the way in which our affiliates and service providers treat your personal information, contact us as set out below.

How do we safeguard your personal information?

We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of personal information in our custody and control. Your online access to certain of your personal information may be protected with a password you select. We strongly recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in any unsolicited communication (such as letters, phone calls or email messages).  

We have personal information retention processes designed to retain personal information of our customers for no longer than necessary for the purposes stated above or to otherwise meet legal requirements.

How will we notify you if this policy changes?

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically to reflect changes to our personal information practices. The revised Privacy Policy will be posted on this Website. We strongly encourage you to please refer to this Privacy Policy often for the latest information about our personal information practices.
